okay so in this lesson I'd like to talk
好的，所以在本课中我想谈一谈
about three things make compile and
关于三件事进行编译和
rebuild you can see here that I have a
重建你可以在这里看到我有一个
project in this project there are three
这个项目中有三个项目
separate modules and in each of these
单独的模块，在每个模块中
modules I have some classes some source
我有一些类的模块一些来源
files that I placed inside them and
我放在其中的文件
let's say we'd like to build one class
假设我们想建立一个班级
inside our primary module say the
在我们的主要模块中说
aquaduct class I open up the AquaDuck
渡槽课程我打开AquaDuck
class you can see there's nothing there
上课你可以看到那里什么都没有
just to demonstrate I'll press control
只是为了演示我会按下控制键
shift f9 to compile just this class
转移f9来编译此类
which you can also find inside the build
您也可以在内部版本中找到
menu here so I'm compiling this
这里的菜单，所以我正在编译
particular class so you can see in the
特定的课程，因此您可以在
output directory here if we open this up
如果打开此目录，则在此处输出目录
you have the AquaDuck class and this is
你有AquaDuck课程，这是
d compiled from the class file so the
d从类文件编译而来
bytecode here is red and using a custom
字节码在这里是红色并使用自定义
b compiler we can read the source code
b编译器我们可以阅读源代码
however it doesn't directly use the
但是它并不直接使用
source inside this file now we can also
现在在此文件中找到源
build this entire module so if you open
构建整个模块，所以如果您打开
up the build menu again you can make
再次打开构建菜单
this module and what this will do is it
这个模块，它将做什么
will take all the classes inside the
将参加所有的课程
module and then compile them and that'll
模块，然后编译它们，这将
be placed inside the output directory
放在输出目录中
here and you should see that momentarily
在这里，你应该马上看到
so you can see all these classes inside
所以你可以在里面看到所有这些类
the primary module here are compiled to
这里的主要模块被编译为
the output directory now let's say we
现在输出目录，我们说
want to add a dependency from the
想要从添加依赖
primary module to the secondary module
主模块到辅助模块
so I can do that by clicking here in my
所以我可以点击我这里的
project structure dialog under
下的项目结构对话框
dependencies and I'll add a module
依赖项，我将添加一个模块
dependency on the secondary module so
对辅助模块的依赖
I'll click OK here and click apply now
我将在此处单击“确定”，然后单击“立即申请”
watch what happens if I make the primary
观看如果我成为主要学生会怎样
module again so if I go here and I click
再次模块，所以如果我去这里，我单击
build and I make this module if you look
构建，如果您看，我将制作此模块
inside the output directory now you can
现在在输出目录中，您可以
see that the secondary module is now
看到辅助模块现在
compiled alongside the primary one now
现在与主要版本一起编译
if we add another dependency from the
如果我们从
secondary module to the tertiary module
第二模块到第三模块
I do the same thing I add module
我做的事情与添加模块相同
dependency here I click OK
依赖这里我单击确定
and apply and now go back into the
并申请，现在回到
primary module and build that module
主模块并构建该模块
then what will happen is it will compile
然后会发生的是它将编译
all three primary secondary and tertiary
全部三个小学，中学
recursively so what it'll do is it'll go
递归，所以它将要做的是
to the least dependent module inside
到内部最少依赖的模块
your dependency graph and then go back
您的依赖图，然后返回
up the stack until it finds all the
直到发现所有
dependencies and it can build your
依赖关系，它可以建立你的
entire project now pay close attention
整个项目现在要密切注意
if I go into the tertiary modules output
如果我进入第三模块的输出
directory and I do a listing of all the
目录，我列出所有
class files here then you'll see the
班级文件，然后您将看到
time stamp is all
时间戳就是全部
22:47 now watch very carefully if I make
22:47现在我要非常小心
any changes to this Aqueduct class say I
这个渡槽类的任何变化都说我
add a hash code method and I save this
添加哈希码方法，然后保存
and I recompile the module so I make the
然后我重新编译模块，所以我做了
module it will make only those files
模块将仅制作那些文件
that have changed in this case only the
在这种情况下，只有
Aqueduct file will be recompiled so if I
渡槽文件将被重新编译，所以如果我
do another listing of this the
做这个的另一个清单
timestamps are exactly the same
时间戳完全相同
inside the tertiary output directory
在第三级输出目录中
22:47 however if I go to the primary
22:47但是如果我去小学
output directory and I do a listing of
输出目录，我列出了
these the aquaduct class alone has a
这些仅渡槽类就有一个
different timestamp so now we have a
不同的时间戳，所以现在我们有一个
very clear idea of exactly what make
关于到底是什么的非常清楚的想法
does in this case make has only
在这种情况下，make仅具有
recompiled those classes which have
重新编译那些具有
changed and any dependencies of the
改变和任何依赖
module recursively similarly make
递归类似地使模块
project will do the exact same thing for
项目将完全相同地做
all modified classes across your entire
您整个的所有修改过的类
project and any source files which they
项目以及他们所使用的任何源文件
may depend on now let's say we'd like to
可能取决于现在，假设我们要
rebuild the entire project what this
重建整个项目这是什么
will do is it will clean out the entire
会做的是它将清除整个
output directory and rebuild the project
输出目录并重建项目
from scratch just illustrate that we'll
从头开始只是说明我们
create a new file here
在这里创建一个新文件
inside the output directory for the
在输出目录中
primary module so you can see this new
主模块，以便您可以看到这个新模块
file here now if we go ahead and rebuild
如果我们继续重建，请立即在此处提交
this project any artifacts which may
这个项目的任何文物可能
have been associated with the old build
与旧版本相关联
will be eliminated
将被淘汰
so it'll completely eliminate everything
这样就完全消除了一切
inside the output directory so make sure
在输出目录中，因此请确保
that you don't have anything important
你没有什么重要的
stored there because we'll be deleted so
存储在这里，因为我们将被删除，所以
that covers the three important aspects
涵盖了三个重要方面
of building a project in IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA中构建项目的过程
make which will recompile any sources
使将重新编译任何源
which have changed since the last
自上次以来发生了变化
compliation and you can do this project
恭维，你可以做这个项目
wide or for a specific module compile
广泛或针对特定模块进行编译
which will build exactly one class the
这将建立一个完全的类
class you've selected and rebuild which
您选择的课程并重建
will recompile everything from scratch
将重新编译所有内容
so now hopefully you have a better idea
所以现在希望你有一个更好的主意
of the three different compliation types
三种不同的恭维类型
and how to use them when building your
以及在构建您的产品时如何使用它们
project thanks for watching and develop
项目感谢您的关注和发展
with pleasure
荣幸